<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Flower</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="open">Open Navigation</string>
    <string name="close">Close Navigation</string>
    <string name="enter_password">Enter Password..</string>
    <string name="flower_recognition_app">Flower Recognition App</string>


    <string name="sunflower">The common sunflower is valuable from an economic as well as from an ornamental point of view.
            The leaves are used as fodder, the flowers yield a yellow dye, and the seeds contain oil and are used for food.
            The sweet yellow oil obtained by compression of the seeds is considered equal to olive or almond oil for table use.
            Sunflower oil cake is used for stock and poultry feeding.
        </string>

    <string name="hibiscus">The Hibiscus flowers are showy and conspicuous. It is usually borne singly but sometimes can be seen
            in clusters. The flowers are trumpet shaped and range in colours of red, orange, yellow, pink or purple.
            There are five or more petals in a Hibiscus flower..</string>

    <string name="lily">The lily is a genus of flowering plant. There are many species of lilies,
            like trumpet lilies and tiger lilies. They are usually quite tall, and are perennials.
            Most lilies grow from a bulb, which in some species develops into a rhizome, which carries small bulbs.
        </string>

    <string name="Rose">Roses are native primarily to the temperate regions of the Northern Hemisphere.
            Many roses are cultivated for their beautiful flowers, which range in colour from white through
            various tones of yellow and pink to dark crimson and maroon, and most have a delightful fragrance,
            which varies according to the variety and to climatic conditions.</string>

    <string name="recyclerview">RecyclerView is the ViewGroup that contains the views corresponding to your data.
        Its a view itself so you add RecyclerView into your layout the way you would add any other UI element.
        Each individual element in the list is defined by a view holder object.
        RecyclerView is a ViewGroup added to the android studio as a successor of the GridView and ListView.
        It is an improvement on both of them and can be found in the latest v-7 support packages.
        It has been created to make possible construction of any lists with XML layouts as an item
        which can be customized vastly while improving on the efficiency of ListViews and GridViews.
    </string>

</resources>